Guide to the Gerard Salton papers
Salton, Gerard papers
- Series IV. Professional Papers Writings Books
  - Concerning the Cornell Library, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - A Theory of Term Importance In Automatic Text Analysis, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - A Vector Space Model for Automatic Indexing, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Content Analysis & Information Retrieval- A Summary, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Precision Weighting- An Effective Automatic Indexing Method, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Cataloging Software Packages for Automatic Document Processing, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - On the Role of Words & Phrases In Automatic Text Analysis, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Effective Information Retrieval Using Term Accuracy, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - The SMART Environment for Retrieval System Evaluation, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Clustered File Generation & it's application to Computer Science Taxonomies, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Mathematics & Information Retrieval, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Term Relevance Weights In Online Information Retrieval, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Generation & Search of Clustered Files, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Towards Paperless Information Systems, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - The Three Clusters In Information Science (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - A Citation Study of Computer Science Literature (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Mathematics & Information Retrieval- Journal of Documentation, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Automatic Term Class Construction Using Relevance- A Summary of work In Automatic Pseudo-classification, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Encyclopedia of Computer Science & technology- SMART, 1979-80 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Automatic Information Retrieval, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - A Progress Report on Information Privacy & Data Security, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Parallel Computations In Information Retrieval (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - The Estimation of Term Relevance Weights Using Relevance Feedback, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - A Term Weighting Model Based on Utility Theory, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Automatic Indexing of Natural Language Texts, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - A Comparison of Search Term Weighting - Term Relevance vs Inverse Document Frequency (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Automatic Query Formulations In Information Retrieval, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Automatic Text Processing Slides (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Automatic Indexing Slides (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Boolean Query Relevance Feedback- Slides (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Extended Boolean Information Retrieval -An Outline (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Flexible Method for Boolean Information Retrieval- International Computing Symposium, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Extended Boolean Retrieval- Slides, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Extended Boolean Information Retrieval, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - An Evaluation of Term Dependence Models on Information Retrieval (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - A Comparison of Two Tern Dependence Models In Information Retrieval (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - A Comparison of Inverted File Searching with Cluster Tree Search Operations, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - A Blueprint for Automatic Indexing, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - A Blueprint for Automatic Boolean Query Processing, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - Series III-Publications, Papers (continued)
  - A Generalized Term Dependent Model In Information Retrieval, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Term Weighting In Information Retrieval Using the Term Precision Model, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - An Automatic Environment for Boolean Information Retrieval, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Boolean Query Formulation with Relevance Feedback, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - A Comparison of Two Methods for Boolean Query Relevance Feedback, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Denver Seminar (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Generalized Term Dependence Model (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Howard Aiken & the Harvard Computation Laboratory, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Inspec Draft, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Local vs Global Processing In Information Retrieval (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Automatic Query Formulation-Slides (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Extended Boolean Information Retrieval (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Extended Boolean Information Retrieval- Slides (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Some Research Problems In Automatic Information Retrieval, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Some Characteristics of Future Information Systems, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Recent Approaches to Indexing & Query Processing at Cornell University, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Extended Boolean Information Retrieval - an outline, 1983-84 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - The Use of Extended Boolean Logic In Information Retrieval, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Extended Retrieval Systems- Slides (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Some Notions about Information Retrieval In Automated Office Environments, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - A Note about Information Science Research, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Automatic Assignment of Soft Boolean Operators, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Automatic Indexing & Clustered File Methodologies Applied to Business Correspondence, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Advanced Feedback Methods In Information Retrieval, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Advanced Information Retrieval Methods, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Another Look at Automatic Text Retrieval Systems, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Automatic Assignment of Soft Boolean Operators, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - On the Representation of Query Term Relations by Soft Boolean Operators, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - On the Use of Term Associations In Knowledge -based Text Processing, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Abstracts of various papers on Information Retrieval, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - A note on Information Retrieval Models & Theories, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Information Retrieval Models- Slides (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Information Retrieval Research (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - The Online Society- Slides (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Passage Retrieval- Slides (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Term Weighting- Slides (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Thoughts regarding the RIA -85 Conference In Grenoble, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Vector Processing System, Probabilistic Model, etc.-Slides (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Another look at Automatic Text Retrieval Systems (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Automatic Information Retrieval-Text Analysis- Notes & Slides, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence for Paper Presentation at ASIS Meeting, Chicago, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Automatic Text Searching-Slides (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Automatic Text Searching Systems- Slides (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - A Comparative Evaluation of Searching by Controlled Language & Natural Language n an Experimental NASA Database (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - ASIS Slides- Design of Automatic Retrieval Systems, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Enhancement of Text Representations Using Related Document Titles, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - A Note about Information Science Research (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Information Retrieval Project at Cornell (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Natural Language Processing In Information Retrieval- An Outline, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Knowledge Based Processing In Text Retrieval- Slides (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - On the Use of Knowledge Bases & Complex Identifiers In Automatic Text Processing, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - On the Use of Knowledge Based Processing In Automatic Text Retrieval, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - On the Use of Term Associations In Automatic Information Retrieval, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Parallel Approaches to Document & Data Retrieval (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Recent Trends In Automatic Information Retrieval (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Some Notions about Information Retrieval In Automated Office Environments, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Advanced Retrieval Slides (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Mind over Machine, The Free Press- New York, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Automatic Text Retrieval (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Automatische Textanalyse-Studientexte, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Series III-Publications, Papers (continued)
  - A Simple Blueprint for Automatic Boolean Query Processing (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Some Thoughts about the Automatic Literary Space, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Syntactic Approaches to Automatic Book Indexing, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Thoughts about Modern Retrieval Technologies, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Selective Text Utilization & Text Traversal, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Recent Trends In Automatic Information Retrieval, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Slides on models used In Belgium, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Professor Dr. Gerard Salton, Cornell University, Haessler Literatur Service, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Historical Perspective- the Past Thirty years In Information Retrieval, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Expert Systems & Information Retrieval, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - On the Relationship between Theoretical Retrieval Models, 1987-88 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Parallel Text Search Methods, 1987-88 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - On the Application of Syntactic Methodologies In Automatic Text Analysis, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Improving Retrieval Performance by Relevance Feedback (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Computer Based Text Retrieval - Encyclopedia of Microsystems, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Automatic Text Indexing Using Complex Identifiers, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Artificial Intelligence Approaches In Information Retrieval, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Attempts to Improve Text Analysis- Slides (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Automatic Processing of Natural Language Text- Slides, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Automatic Text Processing- Slides (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Book Indexing- Slides (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Automatic Information Retrieval- Slides, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Automatic Document Manipulations Based on Language Analysis, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Inverted vs Clustered Search (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Information Science Research- Slides (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Language Understanding- Slides (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - A Note on Automatic Book Indexing, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Slides for IBM Talk (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - On the Use of Spreading Activation Methods In Automatic Information Retrieval, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Term Weighting Approaches In Automatic Text Retrieval, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Syntactic Approaches to Automatic Book Indexing, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Thoughts about Modern Retrieval Technologies, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - On the Use of Spreading Activation Methods In Automatic Information Retrieval, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Content Analysis and Indexing (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Text Analysis- Slides (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Content Analysis and Indexing- Slides (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Slides Survey- Language Processing (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Automatic Information processing- Haessler Literature, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - On the Automatic Generation of Content Links In Hypertext, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Automatic Text Index Using Complex Identifiers, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Automatic Text Structuring Experiments, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - A Comparison Between Statistically & Syntactically Generated Term Phrases (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - A Comparison of Book Indexing Methods, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Automatic Indexing for Retrieval Purposes (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Information Retrieval Using Phrase Generation Methods, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Interactive Retrieval Using Phrase Display Operations, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Effective User- System Interaction In Information Retrieval, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Syntactic Processing In Automatic Information Retrieval- Slides (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - On the Application of Syntactic Methodologies In Automatic Text Analysis, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - On the Use of Clustered File Organizations In Information Search & Retrieval (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - User System Interaction In Automatic Information Retrieval (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Topics In Information Retrieval- Slides, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Slides for Departmental Talks, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Natural Language Text Processing- Slides (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Application of Text Analysis Systems- Slides (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - User System Interaction In Retrieval- Slides (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - New Text Analyses- Slides (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Cornell University Department of Computer Science, Colloquium Slides, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Approaches to Text Retrieval for Structured Documents, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Information Processing & Retrieval- Slides (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Series III-Publications, Papers (continued)vv
  - Gerard Salton- Automatic Information Processing- Haessler, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Automatic Text Structuring Experiments, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Full Text Information Processing Using the SMART System (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Flexible Text Matching for Information Retrieval, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - An Evaluation of Text Matching Systems for Text Excerpts of Varying Scope, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Automatic Text Structuring Experiments, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Text Linking & Retrieval Experiments for Textbook Components, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Automatic Text Structuring & Retrieval Experiments In Automatic Encyclopedia Searching (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Selective Use of Full-Text Databases (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - The Application of Syntactic Methodologies In Automatic Text Analyses, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - A Note on Term Weighting & Text Matching, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Future Prospects for Text Based Information Retrieval, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - A Simple Syntactic Approach for the Generation of Indexing Phrases, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Improving Retrieval Performance on Relevance Feedback, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Automatic Structuring of Text Files, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Automatic Indexing - Slides (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Automatic Text Structuring & Retrieval-Experiments In Encyclopedia Searching, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Developments In Automatic Text Retrieval, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Effective Text Understanding In Information Retrieval, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Global Text Matching for Information Retrieval, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - The SMART Document Retrieval Project, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - The SMART Retrieval Project (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Automatic Determination of Content Relationships In Natural Language Texts, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Approaches to Passage Retrieval In Full Text Information Systems, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - The State of Retrieval System Evaluation (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Theories of Meaning- Slides (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Restriction Evaluations, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Automatic Retrieval with Locality Information Using SMART, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Automatic Information Storage & Retrieval- Slides Survey, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Passage Retrieval- Slides, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Automatic Methods for Text Utilization In Large Full-Text Databases- Lecture & Seminar Slides, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Selective Text Utilization & Text Traversal, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - SMART Systems- Slides, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Slides for SIGIR-'93- Passage Retrieval (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Automatic Text Theme Generation & the Analysis of Text Structure, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Automatic Text Structuring & Text Utilization- Slides, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Text Retrieval Using the Vector Processing Model, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Automatic Analysis, Theme Generation & Summarization of Machine Readable Texts, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Automatic Structuring & Retrieval of Large Text Files, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Automatic Analysis of Machine Readable Texts, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Science Articles, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Selective Text Traversal, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Notes for SIGIR (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Automatic Routing & Ad-Hoc Retrieval Using SMART Trec-2, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Automatic Text Theme Generation & the Analysis of Text Structure, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Associative Retrieval Techniques- General Comments & Proposed Evaluation Experiments (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Automatic Text Decomposition & Structuring, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Basic Tools for Text Manipulation - Slides- Dartmouth, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Automatic Information Storage & Retrieval- Copies of Slides (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Automatic Document Structuring - Slides (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Extended Query Processing - Slides (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Language Structure- B.B.N. Talk- Slides (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Cluster Similarities Superimposed On Hypertext Structure- Slides (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - A Comparison of Search Term Weighting: Term Relevance vs Inverse Document Frequency (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - A Computer Science View Obtained by Automatic Document Processing (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Some Characteristics of Future Information Systems (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Database & Text Retrieval (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - The SMART Automatic Text Processing & Document Retrieval System (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - The Experimental Automatic SMART System & Its Use In Evaluating Retrieval Techniques (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Federal Register- Text Structures- Slides (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Cluster Searching Evaluation- Slides (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Hierarchical Clustering- Slides (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Information Retrieval Approaches- Slides (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Automatic Information Retrieval Survey- Colgate- Slides (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Linguistic Retrieval Model- Slides (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - The Automatic Transcription of Machine Shorthand (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Content Analysis & Indexing (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - A Method for Using Punctuation Patterns In the Machine Translation of Languages (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - On the Future of Mechanized Information Files (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Phrase Generation Methods (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Language Oriented Information Retrieval- Slides (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Natural Language Text Processing- Slides (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Extended Boolean Information Retrieval- Slides for talk In Europe (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Probabilistic Retrieval- Slides (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Queries- Slides (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Sample Comparisons of Text Sections, Paragraphs & Sentence Groups- Slides (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - SMART System Environment- Slides (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Standard Document Processing- Slides (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Syntax Evaluation- Slides (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Text Structuring & Browsing Facilities (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Probabilistic Inference- Slides (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Vector Systems- Slides (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Standard Document Processing Cluster- Slides (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Information Retrieval Models- Slides (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Glossy Prints (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Automatic Query Construction & Extended Boolean Processing (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Text Matches, Queries & Relevance Feedback- Slides (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Slides (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - List of Publications (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - List of Reprints (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Recent Literature Covering Automatic Indexing, Dynamic File Maintenance, SMART Systems (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - A.A.A.S. Meetings & Symposia Correspondence-I (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - A.A.A.S. Meetings & Symposia Correspondence-II (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - A.A.A.S. Section T- Elections (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Proposal for a New ACM Publication- Transactions on Information Storage & Retrieval(TISR) (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - ACM Reports (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Advance Information Systems - Word Association Model (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - AFIPS Material (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Publications by Others
  - Aalbersberg I.J. -POOMA- Parallel Object Oriented Machine-High Quality & High Performance Full Text Document Retrieval (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Aalbersberg I.J. -PRISM- Parallel Inference & Storage Machine- A Parallel Full Text Document Retrieval System (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Aalbersberg I.J. -Information Management- Posting Compression In Dynamic Retrieval Environments (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Aalbersberg I.J. Information Management-Incremental Relevance Feedback- (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Abacus- The Word & The Device (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Abraham C.T., Ghosh S.P.,Roy Chaudhary D.K.-File Organization Schemes Based on Finite Geometrics- (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Abraham C.T -Techniques for Thesaurus Organization & Evaluation (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Agre P.,Chapman D.-PENGI: An Implementation of a Theory of Activity (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Aho A.V., Sagiv T., Ullman J.D.-Efficient Optimization of a Class of Relational Expressions (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Aho A.V., Corasick M.J.-Efficient String Matching: An Aid to Bibliographic Search (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Les Machines A Calculer et La Pensee Humaine (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Proposed Automatic Calculating Machine- H.Aiken (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Aiken H.-Articles & Tributes to Howard Aiken (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Akert K.-Correspondence with Konrad Akert (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Alexander R.W., Harvey R.W.-An Overview of the Experimental Library Management System (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - The Efficiency of Algorithms (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Allen L.-Beyond Document Retrieval Towards Information Retrieval- Federal Estate Tax (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Allan J.-Butterfly & SMART (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Allen J., Green S., Friedman J., Harrington B., Johnson L.-Information Storage & Retrieval by Computer- An Emerging Problem for Law of Copyright (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Altmann B.-The HDL Automatic Information System (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Altmann B.-A Multiple Testing of Natural Language Storage & Retrieval- Preliminary Analysis (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Altmann B .-A Natural Language Storage & Retrieval (ABC Method):Rationale, Operation & Further Development Program (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Altmann B -Automated SDI Services ( Selected Dissemination of Information) (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - American Institute of Physics- Jan 1966- Symposium on Storage & Retrieval of Information (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Amdahl G.M., Blaaw G.A., Brooks Jr, F.P.-Architecture of the IBM System (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - The Ann Arbor Ambassador Terminal (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - American Psychological Association- The Role of the Technical Report In the Dissemination of Scientific Information (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - American Mathematical Society- Research on Machine Aids to an Editor of Scientific Translations (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - American Mathematical Society - Mathematical Offprint Service (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - American Mathematical Society -Development of the Photon for Efficient Mathematical Composition (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Ammon R.V.- Modeling of Office Information Systems (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - Amsler R.A., Simmons R.F.-Modeling Dictionary Data (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - Anderson Arthur Co.-Research Study of Criteria & Procedures for Evaluating Scientific Information Retrieval Systems (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - Anderson D.- Universal Bibliographic Control (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - Anderson R.R.-An Associativity Technique for Automatically Optimizing Retrieval Results (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Andrewsky A., Saclay C.E.A.-Analyse Comparative du Contenu Indexation Automatique (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Andrewsky A., Fluhr C., Debili F.-Computational Learning of Semantic Lexical Relations (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Andrewsky A., Fluhr C., Rambousek J-Automisation de L'Analyse Discriminante, de L'Indexation, de La Recherche Hierarchisee des Documents (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - Andrews G.- Parallel Programs: Proofs, Principles & Practice (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - Publications by Others (continued)
  - Anger- An Algorithm for the Genius of a Graph (Box 31, Folder 1)